{"data":[{"question":"The first truly success helicopter was designed by the German engineer Heinrich Focke.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"for","b":"well-rounded education","c":"espoused","d":"in time of","answer":"4","explain":" - In time of-> at the time of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Our new neighbors had been living in Arizona since ten years before moving to their present house.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"personnel","b":"theirselves","c":"by the","d":"expression","answer":"2","explain":" - Theirselves-> themselves","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Air pollution, together with littering, are causing many problems in our large, industrial cities today.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In the spirit","b":"naturalist","c":"author's","d":"surviving","answer":"4","explain":" - Surviving-> survival","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The need for a well-rounded education was an idea espoused by the Greeks in time of Socrates.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Stephen Crane's story","b":"a","c":"of man as an animal","d":"the fear","answer":"4","explain":" - The fear-> fear","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"While searching for the wreckage of a unidentified aircraft, the Coast Guard encountered severe squalls at sea.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"succeeded","b":"on","c":"more and more","d":"on","answer":"2","explain":" - On-> in\nSucceed in doing something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Although a number of police officers was guarding the priceless treasures in the museum, the director worried that someone would try to steal them.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"this","b":"have been known","c":"as","d":"law enforcers","answer":"1","explain":" - This-> these","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Since it was so difficult for American Indians to negotiate a peace treaty or declare war in their native language, they used a universal understood form of sign language.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"never","b":"an","c":"to play","d":"in","answer":"1","explain":" - Never-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Louis Braille designed a form of communication enabling people to convey and preserve their thoughts to incorporate a series of dots which were read by the finger tips.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"with","b":"are","c":"many","d":"in our large","answer":"2","explain":" - Are-> is\nSometimes the subject is separated from the verb by words such as along with, as well as, besides, or not. Ignore these expressions when determining whether to use a singular or plural verb.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"While verbalization is the most common form of language in existence, humans make use of many others systems and techniques to express their thoughts and feelings.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Because of","b":"the","c":"dropped food","d":"close the city","answer":"4","explain":" - Close-> close to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Writers and media personnel sell theirselves best by the impression given in their verbal expression.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the only birds","b":"to fly","c":"as well as","d":"forward","answer":"2","explain":" - To fly-> of flying","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}